Thank you. My name is Dove. Bunch of
these songs if you didn't recognize them
were originals. And um I got this guitar
case here which is pretty empty if
anyone wants to make any contributions.
I will accept that. And there's also a
Venmo QR code here on on the little
side. So thank you dove D O V. And I'm
going to bring up right now your MC.
That's spelled MC. And uh here he comes,
your master of ceremonies. One step at a
time. He's still learning to walk. And
please give it a warm welcome for Chino
La Forge.
You could do better than that.
>> Hey, keep it going for Dove, ladies and
gentlemen. The opening musical act of
the evening. Keep it going for Dove.
>> Thank you.
>> Wow. You didn't keep it going long. Is
that okay? Hey, is everybody okay?
>> What's going on? Did you guys all get
broken up via text message on the way
here? What happened? I'm so sorry.
You're better than them. You don't need
that. Welcome to PA Coffee and Bar for
the Comedy Simulator. Who's here for
comedy tonight?
>> Okay. Who is in fact not here for
comedy? They're here for dinner and
comedy is just kind of happening at
them.
>> Okay. Good. Good. Those are the people
that we always worry about because you
never know if they're going to like it,
hate it. complain about in Yelp. We've
got a couple. It happens. It's part of
the nature of the beast. But this is the
comedy simulator every Monday at 7:15 on
the dot here at Pa Bay. Um, whose first
time is it here at the Comedy Simulator?
First- timers, where you at?
>> 1 2
three. Thank you for your honesty. Wow,
very few first- timers. That's good.
That means we have a lot of repeat
offenders. What did you do? What's going
on here, weirdos? Why you like this?
Anyways, uh this is not a real comedy
show. This is a simulated comedy
experience.
>> What does that mean?
>> We are not real comedians.
>> You are not a real audience.
>> What does that mean?
>> No, no one charged you for a cover
charge. So, lower your expectations,
friends.
We are not selling you anything. There's
nothing for sale. There's nothing to
buy. Also, you're gonna see a wide range
of art tonight. Okay? You're gonna see
some fine china art and you're going to
see some paper plate art. All right?
You're going to get the full gambit.
>> You're on the cutting edge of comedy and
sometimes the cutting edge of something
looks like it's bad comedy. That kind of
they go hand in hand. Uh that's what
cutting edge technology looks like. You
never buy first gen. This is first
generation comedy. Comedians are
figuring out their material in front of
you. You're going to see moments of
brilliance and you're going to see some
tough ones, too. It's kind of a part of
the show. That's why we're here. We're
also live streaming tonight's events on
YouTube as we do every week. Check out
our channel at Comedy Simulator. Thank
you for watching. Whoever's watching
right now, please like, subscribe, all
the things. Um, last week we had 75,000
viewers tune in
>> for what? I don't know. Whatever. It's
either us or like Chinese food trucks.
So, this is what they get at this time
of night. This is the only thing on live
streams. We're happy you're here. Thanks
for joining us. Uh if you join the
comment section, you'll see that they
are uh they're terribly rude to us.
That's part of the fun, too. Feel free
to say terrible things about us in the
comment section. We're all kind of about
it. We do a theme every week. Last week,
what was last week's theme, Skyler? Do
you remember?
>> It was duets. That's right. We had two
comics on stage at a time. Not this
week. This week, we're doing crowd work
or no, not crowd work. Excuse me. We're
doing characters. What is characters?
Well, every comedian use character work
sometime in their comedy skits, whether
they're doing conversation with other
people or they go into a bit where
they're becoming somebody. Um, it's
convoluted. I'll explain it a little bit
uh through my set as well, but every
comedian tonight is going to be doing
characters in their set if they can.
It's not a mandatory thing. You can not
follow the rules and I'm pretty sure
there's a drinking game online for
people who do that, too. Uh, but try to
do characters. That's the attempt.
audience member of the night. Guess
what? You get a free bottle of High
Spice hot sauce.
That's right. Our sponsor, our place of
refuge, highspice. Check them out.
Highspice.com. Go ahead and bring up
that. You already did. Uh,
Comm. If you're on our online store,
we'll get you 10% off your order. It's
not just hot sauce. We got hats, we got
shirts, we got all types of awesome
stuff. Subscription packs. Check it out
now. highspice.com, not to be confused
with hospice.com.
One letter away, very different service.
Um, both make you wish you were gone.
All right, so uh let's see. We got that
bang bang bang. Um, comic of the night.
We sometimes announce, sometimes we
don't. We'll find out. Maybe the the
online has a favorite one, too. We'll
figure it out. All right, come in. You
should get five minute sets. We know the
rules. We're ready to start this
character comedy night.
Well, that hardly sounds like consent.
Are we ready to start this character
night of the comedy simulator?
>> Well, let's do it. Begin simulation.
All right. So, I I I've done a lot of
improv in my career, and instead of just
pulling out a character, which I can
easily do, uh I'm going to build a
character with you on stage, and then
we're going to do a little little fun
with it. Um, sometimes characters come
from things of like technique and study.
Sometimes they come from weird people
that you meet. Uh, I had a property
owner in Wuku that I'll never forget.
It's like oh, hey, oh, you know, Jesus
Christ, buddy, you know, you got to pay
rent. You got to pay. You know,
everybody's got characters. You got to
find out what makes people characters.
So, we're going to do that right now.
So, we're going to do a little call and
response and you guys are going to help
me build this person. Okay. So, first
off, this character, where do they lead
from? What's the part of their body
that's the most prevalent?
>> All right, crotch is a little easy.
>> We can do crotch if you want to. Do you
want a crotch that bad?
>> Audience, do you guys want you want a
crotch character?
>> Jimbo, I'm not listening to you. You're
not audience. You're not audience.
You're you're agent of chaos and I don't
listen to you.
>> All right.
Give you the crotch. All right, fine.
I'll give you the crotch. That is um
>> Let's see. What kind of animal
represents this character's personality?
Give me any type of wild animal
>> or could be an insect. Anything.
>> Sloth.
>> A sloth. A crotch sloth. Already off to
a good start. All right. Wonderful.
What's this person a specialist in? What
does he know a lot about? What is he
talking to you about today?
>> Football.
Come on. Really?
This guy sounds like my dad. This is so
boring. What are we doing here, guys?
>> A school shoot.
>> Whoa. Okay, that is
>> careful what you wish for, Chino. Right.
That is like He's a specialist in
football. No. School shootings. Ooh,
that's a Are you one of those people
that just go to improv shows just to
yell terrible things and watch them
wiggle? Is this Ted? Is that what we're
doing? All right.
>> 911. Hey,
>> it is No, I
>> No, cuz Brady's doing a set later and I
don't want to step on everything he's
going to say.
>> I feel like that's going to be his All
right, give me a specialist in
something. Come on, give me something.
>> I already have a hot sauce specialist.
>> Foot care.
>> Foot care. A podiatrist. A pedto. All
right, got it.
>> A crotch sllo pedto. That's what I'm
doing. You guys ready? Here we go.
What's up everybody? My name's Man. I'm
going to show you everything there is to
know about setting up your orthopedics
for your feet. Now, it's important to
remember that feet go heel to toe, not
toe to heel. If you push your podiatrist
in toe to heel, you going to be walking
backwards everywhere you go. And that's
not going to work for you, right? So,
make sure you sync up your left foot
with your left pad. done that before,
too. You ever put a right pad on left
foot? You're gonna be walking in
circles. Ain't going to work for you,
fella. All right. So, don't forget,
first thing you got to do is you got to
boil this pad. Boil this pad. You got to
boil this pad. What does that mean? Boil
this pad. It's exactly what it sounds
like. It's exactly what it sounds like,
right? You put that pad in the water.
You boil it. You put it to your feet.
Why does it smell like Fritos? Cuz you
didn't wash your feet. You wash the pad.
That's a problem, right? Better wash
that pad. Wash that foot. Put it on your
feet. Now, here's a couple of frequently
asked questions about these pads that we
have for sale here. They said, "What if
this pad doesn't reach quiet to my
toes?" Well, then son, you just got a
youth pad. We're not going to have that.
That's a pedto pad. We need a big pad
for this failure over here. So, that's a
basic concept for a character. There you
go.
You got it. All right. Uh, comedians are
going to be trying to slide characters
into their sets. However you want to do
it organically, whether you're the
character, you're talking to the
character, how you want to do it. I want
to see it. That's what we're about. You
guys ready to start this comedy
simulator? We're doing it. Are we doing
it?
>> All right. Does anybody want to dive on
the on the grenade and get the first set
in tonight? We got Ivan first on the
list, but does anybody want to jump for
Joshua? Was that Were you just going to
the bathroom? Was that a request? I'll
do it.
>> You'll You'll do it. You'll do it.
Ladies and gentlemen, the first
character of the night, the poet and the
comedian. Give it up for Joshua.
>> I remember what I was going to do.
All right.
All
right.
>> Jesus,
the
the second coming, aka Charles Manson.
I'm uh back.
Everybody seems disappointed.
All right. Um
Um
This is my uh
this is my uh angel talking to me.
I think I got that. What was that?
That's kind of [ __ ] up, but you know,
it's what you what you say, I guess. So,
um
um this is my uh Trump impersonation.
Actually, I'm speechless. Um
uh this is my uh Netany and Yahoo
impersonation. Uh
Jews, am I right?
Um
this is my uh Chino impersonation of
talking about me with milk.
Um, uh,
the
joke sat on a shelf in the dark for so
long that for, uh, months. Uh, he's
going to bring it back. One second. I
got to go get it.
brought it back out as raw cheese.
>> He's a dairy boy. Joshua, ladies and
gentlemen. Um, yes. The first time he
joined us, he was drinking an entire
gallon of milk. And uh that's what he
was referencing.
>> I still don't have an explanation as to
why he was drinking a full gallon of
milk. Uh I guess that's what Jesus turns
water into these days. All right. Uh
coming on stage who is ready to go in
the top of the list, ladies and
gentlemen. Just had a show recently at
the playground and will be there again
this Thursday for Auntie Carol Lee's
fundraiser. Give it up for Ivan Nensson.
I heard that.
Oh, the chair.
You don't use the chair. Who said that?
All right. You better.
I How are you?
my mind I would I don't remember my name
but hi
>> do you know do you know how do you call
redhaired Jewish people
redhaired Jewish people are orange juice
you want to learn where I learned that.
No, you don't.
You know, I live in Haiku and people in
high school because it's all very wet,
people ask me, "How mold are you?
How mold are you?"
Moldiness, I say.
And then
the other day I told my neighbor that I
just I felt
like the X Files, you know, but I I I
where is my scaly? I I feel molder.
Okay.
Okay, that's it for that, right?
Thank you so much.
Ah,
this is itchy, by the way.
>> Thank you so much.
How many of you know me?
>> Yeah. All right. I don't feel alone. All
right. Beautiful. Okay. For those who
don't know me, I am bisexual, which
means I have ladies I have twice the
opportunity of getting, you know,
ghosted.
I get ghosted a lot.
My sex life is a paranormal activity.
Yeah. Because never happens, but when it
does, no one believes me.
It's amazing.
Let me tell you a little bit more about
myself. Uh the other day I was talking
to a woman and she said, "Do you live
alone?" And I said, "Yes." And she went
like, "Okay, let's do something." It was
midnight
and I'm like, "Okay,
do you want to come over?" And she went
like, "Yeah, of course." So 200 the
night and 600 for the whole weekend.
And I'm like, "You're kidding me, right?
I was just about to give you my rates."
She couldn't afford me.
If you're interested, I have an only
men.
It's 10 $10 a month.
>> Only men. Okay. Beautiful.
Don't you like the silence on stage?
It's beautiful. It kills your ears.
Every time I I tell people that I have a
new grill, they check my teeth.
And I hate that. I hate that because
people don't like like barbecues and
stuff. They just prefer looking at you
going like, "Oh, you look like you just
blew C3PO. It's amazing."
One minute of this.
>> I'm gonna
I don't know. I'm going to leave you
with this.
The OG Egyptians were black. Do you know
this?
That's why the real name of Tuton common
was Tuton. Come on, man.
>> All right.
My name is Ivan. Thank you so much.
Keep it going for Ivan, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> I always love it when somebody on the
queer spectrum plays an an older person
because for gay men, an older person's
like 42. It's like an old queen. They
don't come out anymore. Um
Oh, so none of you have gay friends. All
right, I get it. I get it. It's one of
those rooms. Got it. Got it. Feels like
Midwest at Christmas. Wonderful. Ready
for that? Wonderful.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, your
next comic runs the Tuesday mic in
Kihei. If this isn't enough open mic
comedy for you, I don't know why it
isn't, but if it isn't, you can get
another night of it. Give it up for Mr.
Morgan Tmasian.
>> Hey everybody, good to be back here in
PA.
How's everybody doing out there?
Well,
medium
rare.
>> My girlfriend called me today.
She said, "Your dog pooped on the lai."
I said, "Thanks, babe. I will put a
paper towel over it until you get home."
Hey, welcome back from Birding Man.
everybody who was there. Good to have
you back. You got the dust washed off.
Good to see you. Uh I never been to
Burning Man. I watched it about dozen
years in a row though on the internet.
It gets better every year. This year
seemed very Disneyland to me though. And
by Disneyland I mean I can't afford it.
I uh and then and it's funny because
like you know they're making things
they're talking about making things
affordable like going to Mars.
Affordable for who? Billionaires.
We have any billionaires in here
tonight? Anybody going to Mars? The uh
the thing about it is
it's affordable. It's going to be
affordable one day. It's expensive now,
but it's going to be affordable one day.
They can't even make Disneyland
affordable.
Like kids are like asking their parents,
"When are you going to go to
Disneyland?" And they're like, "You did
go when you were two and you loved it
cuz it was free."
Anyway, uh I ran to uh let's see. Uh but
no, it's good to be back uh here. Uh
let's see, what else was I going to say?
uh back in the room uh full of people
who are qualified to be our national
defense secretary. Yeah, it's really
nice, you know, very very reassuring.
Um you know, are we at war? I don't
know. Are we in a ceasefire? I don't
know. Is it one of those insider trading
ceasefires? I have no idea.
And just like all y'all, when he started
bombing Iran
like you, I was like, "What is in the
rest of those Epstein files?"
Godamn. Guy's bombing everything.
Bombing Venezuela.
He's bombing boats off of Mexico. He's
bombing Iran. He bombed the World Cup
photo of the winning team. What was it?
Spain. He bombed that. I mean, [ __ ] Uh,
yeah. Anyway, uh, enough about him. Him.
They say, uh, Bill Gates,
no, no, no, excuse me. Steve Jobs. Steve
Jobs had he lived, he he might have been
a better president than Donald Trump,
but that would be like comparing apples
to oranges.
I know it's getting bad. Oh man, the
kids are having Jamaican hair week next
week. I'm dreading it.
Uh let's see. And uh yeah though uh
there's some there's some good things
happening uh but I can't seem to talk
about them lately. Got a lot of
problems. I made a support group for
adult children of fathers who should
have pulled out of the driveway.
Um
what happened? Oh man. Yeah. No, they
told me I should get in tr They told me
I should get in touch with my inner
child and I didn't know that I was
pregnant.
I uh my boobs were swollen, but I didn't
know. You know what I mean? It's just
such a shock. Uh anyway, uh yeah, let's
see. We got some we got some comedians
here. Uh I I forgot to do my character.
Uh, so yeah, I hope we see some other
good stuff tonight cuz uh
we need a little bit of a wake up. You
know what I'm saying? All right, I'm
out. Thanks.
>> I've heard more claps than an AA
meeting. Give it up for Morgan Tom
Asian, ladies and gentlemen.
He's doing his best. That's a character.
That's his that that's him trying to
pretend like he is an upright citizen.
And I appreciate it. Thank you for
making the effort to be here sober
enough to go through traffic court. That
is as much as we can expect from him.
One more time for Morgan, ladies and
gentlemen.
All right. What's going on? Is this
because it's like close to the year
anniversary of Charlie Kirk's death? Is
that what's is that why you guys are
acting like this? You got we we already
cried as a nation once. Do we need to do
that again? All right, moving right
along. Ladies and gentlemen, coming up
next to the stage, a person who showed
up in character. I don't know how else
to introduce her, but give it up for
>> Hi,
>> I'm Shmmermore and I'm not going to take
it anymore.
Who the hell are you? Shane, looking at
me, your crazy hat. I see you, Jackson.
>> You did nothing wrong.
I had a nuclear family and we had a
meltdown.
Got too toxic. I have a stay-at-home
mom. Um, I had a stay-at-home dad, too.
They stayed at different homes.
Oh, where is this?
My mom went on maternal leave, but she
didn't come back. That's okay. Sh me
shmore more don't care.
Spirymore
takes takes it as it comes.
Um, so anyhow, I was raised by my dad.
Uh, my dad was a single parent. So, if
you want someone to sing you a song or
knit you a sweater, I'm not your girl.
But if you want someone to change your
tire, rewire a lamp, or pull you a pull
martini, I'm your man.
Smurmore.
I um
I'm going back to men cuz scissoring
ain't cutting it.
Smurmore.
Um see, my dad didn't have a job. He was
stay at home dad cuz he had crazy
checks. I'm like, "Kaching."
I um when I moved away, I got 300 bucks
a month. That's money in the bank. 15
years old, that's a lot of money.
>> I left a home at 16, but uh
uh that was Thanks, Uncle Sam. Let's
see. My dad would uh bring trees into
the house sometimes for uh when it
wasn't any reason really, just for the
birds that he brought in the house.
He would make me uh trick-or- treat when
it wasn't Halloween. He'd make me
trick-or- treat in June. So, I'd be
like, "Dad, I don't want to do this."
And he's like, "Come on, Corky." And he
put me in a clown costume and make me go
to the neighbors.
My sister was even more mad. She's in a
kimono. And he's like, "You get over
there and you get the go
trick-or-treating."
But we got changed. So, anyone else do
that?
Smurfy. Smur don't care.
That's okay. Um, I took my situationship
to the situation room.
That's a good one. I like it one. Let's
see where else.
Well, smirky my schmirks. I don't know
if I have anything left, but thanks for
for coming.
What a live crowd we got.
>> Calling it a quick one. Shmeirmore.
everybody here.
Oh, I love I love traumatizing stories
about fathers. Uh I got one. You guys
want to hear a quick one real quick
before bring the comic up?
>> Um so my Oh, no. I already told this one
last week, right? About the the pying
they did. Skyler, were you there for
that?
>> Talked about the cake.
>> I don't remember the cake.
>> Okay, I'll just retell it. It's a new
audience. All right. So, uh, every year
my dad got me with the same [ __ ]
prank on my birthday. He'd cut a piece
of my cake. He'd smell it and be like,
"Hey, son. This cake smells funny." And
I'd always go in to smell it. And every
year he'd [ __ ]
three years in a row until one day on
4th of July, my mom made this red,
white, and blue cake. White bananas with
whipped cream, red strawberries,
blueberries. The thing looked
incredible.
cut a slice. I smelled it. I was like,
"Dad, something about this cake smells
funny." He goes, "No way. Really?" He
put it up to his face. I got excited.
And instead of pying my dad in the face,
I went, "You can." I [ __ ] suck. I
just slugged this cake dead up his nose
like he ate cake from the back of his
throat.
>> And I found out that day that dad jokes
are only funny if you're the dad. Uh, I
got the [ __ ] kicked out of me. Uh, and I
don't smell cake anymore. Um,
Corki is just like one of those moments
like, "Wait, that's not I thought that
was No. All right, I'll just save that
one for my therapist." You're fine. All
right, we're going to keep this moving
right along. If you think that was
traumatizing, wait until what this next
comic does to you. Ladies and gentlemen,
I don't know if you're ready. I don't
even know if he's a character. I don't
know what he's doing tonight. Simply
known as Dumpster Danny. Dumpster Danny.
How we doing tonight?
>> Where's all my drunk ass ladies tonight?
You know, I always wish there were they
would start some kind of like, you know,
national drunk ladies day because if it
wasn't for our drunk ass women and our
drunk ass decisions and their drunk ass
ways,
we would like have no one to talk to,
you know? It would almost make it
impossible for guys like me to get laid.
So, keep on drinking, ladies.
How you guys all doing tonight?
>> So, tonight's comedy theme is
characters. Is that correct?
>> So, I was watching the movie Bambi the
other night. One of the best American
war movies I've ever seen.
That's right, folks. You think Bamiy's
mom was killed by a hunter? [ __ ] no, she
wasn't. She was shot down by a German
sniper.
And Bambi's father planned the whole
thing.
Gee, Dad, why did you let mom die like
that? Why didn't you go after and
protect her? Shut the [ __ ] up, Bammy.
Your mom knows damn well what kind of
dear I was before she married me.
And you know what else too, Bambi? Your
mom also knows how many [ __ ] [ __ ]
I [ __ ] behind her back, including her
sister.
>> And your stupid friend Thumper was there
to watch it, too. And he enjoyed
watching it. Gee, Dad, why would you do
something like that to mom? Look here,
Bambi. I don't got time to argue with
your ass, okay?
It's like, I'm your [ __ ] father, so
you need to start doing what it's told.
You understand? Yes, father, I
understand. But what about mom?
Shouldn't we at least give her a nice
pretty tombstone and bury her somewhere?
Yeah. Yeah, Bambi, that's a good idea.
As a matter of fact, before we do any of
that, I just want to [ __ ] your mom one
last time. But Dad, why would you want
to do that for? Mom's already dead.
Because that's the way I like it, Bambi.
Because that's the way I like it.
>> Oh boy.
So, how many people here tonight have
ever smoked like a joint with their
group of friends, thinking of ways of
how to rob a bank without getting
caught?
>> Those were always the most glory days,
weren't they, folks?
>> All right, so there's like five of us,
right?
And I already know that the bank we're
going to rob got five cameras to the
right,
>> four cameras to the left.
>> I don't know how many cameras in the
back, but that's okay because we're not
going to be there too long anyhow.
But how long are we going to be in the
bank for?
2 minutes. Nothing more longer than
that. We'll have our getaway driver wait
for us in the car.
But but but what about everything else?
I mean, what about the all the customers
and and the damn bank tellers? I
wouldn't worry about that. Those guys
are nothing to worry about.
Those [ __ ] are always getting
ballsy, too, trying to play the damn
hero. But we're not going to worry about
that [ __ ] right now.
Thank you folks. That's all I got.
Say what you want to about his content.
The boy brought characters. All right.
He voiced like four different people.
It's character night.
He at least gets that. That's like at
least a C plus. Uh everybody okay? By
the way, everybody, you know, we also
have uh prevention hotlines that you can
call if you need it on deck waiting for
you. Uh ladies and gentlemen, your next
comic um should be some sour cream on
that spicy taco, right? We just we just
ate something that might have burned our
tongues a little bit. This might be a
pallet cleanser. We'll find out. Ladies
and gentlemen, get up for Joel Huitt.
Woo.
Okay, for my first character, I'm gonna
pretend to be somebody who's having a
good time tonight. Am I right?
Come on, guys.
>> Can we all Can we all pretend to be that
character for my next set, please?
Please. Let's see here. Uh, character
number one. This is a guy who's so horny
that it physically hurts, right?
What's up, man? Can I get 20 on pump
three?
>> That was a good one. Here's that here's
that same guy getting pulled over by the
cops. Uh, sir, can I get license and
registration?
Sir, step out of the vehicle. Listen, if
you handcuff me, this is only going to
get worse.
All right, that's good. It's good medium
response.
It's good medium response. Good ego
boost for my third joke. That's great.
All right. Uh, my next character is
Chino earlier today.
Oh man. Yeah, I'm living life. It's
good. I'm enjoying myself. Oh, [ __ ]
It's Monday night.
[ __ ] dude. I got to think of a topic
tonight. [ __ ] I wish I could just be
somebody else for just one second.
Characters. We're doing characters
tonight, everybody.
All right, my uh my next impression is
of one of our fellow comics, Chuck
Thompson. All right, here we go.
Aloha,
everybody.
Boop boop boop boop.
That's a 10 out of 10 Chuck
impersonation.
Thank you. Thank you for those of you
who know. Um, my next one will be a
Shane Nelson impersonation. Here we go.
>> Hi everybody. I'm Shane Nelson. Uh,
Costco bag. I have a three-legged dog
named Bry. All right, that's all I got.
Um, my next one is going to be of
Jackson, our our beloved Jackson.
Yeah, man. I don't know. At any given
moment, I have no idea what the [ __ ] is
going on.
All right. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Um, my
next uh my next character is going to be
our beloved Jimbo. Um, this is my best
impersonation of Jimbo.
How about the Jews? Am I right? All
right, that's all I got for Jimbo. Um,
let's see. I'm going to try this. We're
going to try and make something together
for those of you who I haven't
completely turned off to this set. thus
far. Um, we're going to do a who, what,
where. All right, give me the first who.
What country am I from?
>> Somebody yell something out.
>> Algeria.
>> I don't know what Algerian accents.
>> Where?
>> If you can both do it at the same time
so I couldn't hear either one of you,
that would be [ __ ] awesome.
>> Denmark.
>> Denmark. All right. The the b the
benefit for me there is that nobody in
this room knows what somebody from
Denmark sounds like. So I have that
working to my advantage.
>> All right. Uh the what what is this guy
from Denmark doing? Somebody give me
something.
>> Huh?
>> Changing a Changing a light bulb.
>> All right. Changing a Changing a light
bulb. And where is this guy from Denmark
changing this light bulb?
Anybody?
>> No.
>> Denmark.
>> In Denmark. All right, here we go.
Ready? Full commitment. A guy from
Denmark changing a light bulb in
Denmark. Here we go.
Yeah, this is very good. We go righty
tighty, lefty loosey. Oh, it's on. Look
at that. Academy Award-winning
performance. Thank you everybody. I'm
out of here.
And just like more people from Denmark,
he's sexier when he doesn't talk. Joel
Huins, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, sorry. Did I nail that too hard for
a couple people? Okay. All right. Um,
ladies and gentlemen, come up next to
the stage. Someone I have to lift the
microphone stand for greatly. Giant of a
man. Uh, he runs our uh AI applets for
our You know what? We'll tell you about
that. That that's that's that's for when
we start to close stuff. Ladies and
gentlemen, again for Mr. E.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. The the
AI atlas China was talking about it. It
all started when I said, "What are these
[ __ ] on live chat saying about me?
Am I saying anything funny?" And come to
find out, there's thousands of comments
in the night. So, you know, me being an
industrious, I I was like, you know
what? This is a perfect thing for AI.
So, I started programming AI to go
through comics and I eventually evolved
it into a full-on website for comedians
accent access where they can go watch
their act specifically, see the live
chats and their dialogue, as well as
sign up for the show on Mondays and
like, you know, just get a good gist of
what's happening. So, the site is called
setpulse.live live if you're interested
to watch and see what people say about
us. On that note, I'm gonna actually try
and be funny. It's pretty funny for me
to think I'm a web designer, but on that
note, character night.
Zoinks.
Cheetos said I'd get a sandwich if I
just spilled the dirt.
I remember being on the show. Those
[ __ ] told me if I just remembered
some lines, they'd give me as many
sandwiches as I could eat.
Just make every single sandwich ever got
stolen by that [ __ ] dog.
That damn dog supposed to be my friend.
Not one sandwich.
Not one time do you make me a And what
the hell they put in those Scooby
snacks? All it does is make me more
sandwiches.
I don't even remember after the Scooby
snacks rolled through. And what will it
take for Fred to share a piece? Gosh,
I'm always stuck with the dog while he's
getting the tail. Zoinks.
Yeah,
>> man. I'll never do that show again.
Every year some other sucker gets sucked
into plain shaggy.
Well, I hope you all know you're trying
to beat me unsuccessfully.
Man, man,
just hearing that makes me want to smoke
a bong. Fortunately for me, you can do
my bongs online as long as you're not
from Pennsylvania.
[ __ ] Pennsylvania.
>> Does anybody else know about that? How
Tommy Tong went to jail for a year
because somebody in Pennsylvania bought
a pipe online?
Man,
what a legend, man. Anyway, Dave's not
home, bro.
No, he's not here, bro.
I I I I was a little I was like
obviously I can do shaggy cuz I'm
basically Shaggy anyways. I'm pretty
much goofy. If you know me in person,
you'll see how clumsy, but I always pull
it off. But honestly, I feel like I'm
already my own characters. I mean, I I
could spend five minutes listing off the
nicknames people try to give me that. I
didn't call start calling myself
mystery. I got this Nick's name. I got
this name from elders with love and
appreciation endearment. It's all the
other nicknames you got to use mystery
to hide over. But I mean, you know,
speaking of characters, I definitely
qualify as a disco druid.
There isn't any music, so you can't see
my dancing.
I would. And and yeah, I'm not allowed
to bring up a a portfolio of all the
flowers and plants I've grown, but you
would be impressed.
Speaking of characters, I I mean also I
mean being a a a demolition expert
veteran is a character in its own right.
You wouldn't believe some of the I I
used to be Christian and there I was on
a Shinook helicopter, the only vehicle
in creation that can crash into itself
in the sky because these two propellers.
There I am barely hearing anything. And
the the
battalion chaplain comes on right before
we're about to fly to Biop Hospital
where this is OF3. This is 2005. So like
guns are firing like we're not allowed
to fly in on C1430s
because they get blown out of sky with
mortars when I'm flying in. And we're on
this Chinook and and the this is my last
moment of being a Christian. the the
chaplain got on and said there's a
misprint in the Bible in the fourth
commandment. It says, "Thou shalt not
kill, but it meant to say, "Thou shalt
not murder." You're allowed to kill for
Jesus and your country. So, go get him.
>> And that was when I stopped being
Christian.
And later I realized there is a
difference between like what Yeshua, the
son of man taught and canonized
Christianity from 292 AD when a Caesar
said, "Let's make everybody easier to
rule." And so they made Christianity and
sheep. And I I like to think of myself
as more of like a guard dog than a
sheep. So I'm not a Christian anymore,
but I do like reading Nagamati.
Getting extra nerdy. I think I'm almost
done. I better crack off with one more
joke. Oh yeah, my life. On that note,
here goes back to Chino. Once again, my
name is Mystery. Thank you everybody.
Have a great night.
Mystery, ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, you ever be sitting on your uh
grandpa's lap as a kid and he's like
bouncing on his knee and all of a sudden
he starts talking about the war and then
his knee stops bouncing
and then your grandma's like, "Okay,
time to grab him off the lap." I feel
like we all experienced that together.
No.
>> All right. Maybe we could talk about it
as a family later. Ladies and gentlemen,
come up to the stage. Speaking of
family, brought her mom. Give it up to
one of our favorites, Miss Emily.
>> Going for Chino. Thank you. Did you miss
me? Anybody miss me? You missed me. You
missed me. Now you got to kiss me.
Anyways, it's been a while since I've
been here. Life's really been grabbing
me by the balls. You know what I mean?
And I feel like a little butterfly. Not
quite a butterfly yet. Kind of still a
caterpillar stuck in the goo. What to do
about that?
I'll get my wings and fly again someday.
But right now, I'm enjoying being stuck
in the goo, staying grateful,
and finding joy
in the little things, and remembering to
continue to love people.
Well, um I don't know what to say. I
guess I'm my own character
and like I said before, I identify as
being on the spectrum and I have a tiny
bit Asberers. So, I guess I would have
to say I identify as having sliders.
Yeah, it's
it's kind of tough
um being on the spectrum and trying um
not to be distracted by things. Um when
I was younger, I was a little bit
distracted by things that um you know,
addicted to what the dick did. But um
I'm over that.
But um so now I'm wishing and hoping
that someday I can have my own dick. No.
So what I did is I borrow I ordered
something online. Okay. I've only
ordered one thing online ever in my
life. Then this is real. And you know
how they say you order one? Well, why
not order eight? Because then you can
get it's a better deal if you order
eight of them. We'll give you a good
deal on them. So I ordered this thing.
It's a necklace, right? And you pull the
string and the the dick goes up. Like a
boner necklace. Like seriously, you pull
the string and the boner goes up. I
seriously have eight of those. And it's
the only thing I've ever ordered online
cuz I wanted my own dick so bad. And cuz
once you have one, you don't really want
one cuz you have one anyways.
So yeah, that's my sad life.
And when I was a kid, I grew up here on
Maui. I went to um Kula Elementary
School and um they used to tease me cuz
my last name was Barton and I had big
boobs. So they would call me Dolly
Parton, right? Rest in peace, Dolly
Parton. But then they'd also call me um
Melly because the the um the substitute
teacher when it wasn't my mom. My mom
was a substitute teacher sometimes, too.
That's embarrassing. But the other
substitute didn't know how to say my
name, so she would pronounce it smelly.
Everybody would laugh. My last name was
Barton, so they would call me smelly
farting Barton. And I had cheese
earlier, so excuse me if I I might fart.
That's my funnest thing to do, you know,
and I like sometimes I get a big one
going and I'm like, "Oh god, I hope my
roommate didn't hear that."
Anyways, who likes to fart here? Anybody
else like to fart? Anyways, you eat the
chi, then you can get a good one going.
Things you can do when you're single
or when you have the love of your life
and you can easily fart together. That's
the best, isn't it? Anybody want to have
a good time farting around? Cuz they
also call me Miss Piggy when I was a kid
cuz I I guess I resemble her cuz I'm so
glamorous and beautiful like Miss Piggy
and I just want to cur me. I have a lot
of love to give. And seriously, if you
miss me, you really have to kiss me. So,
let's go. Come on. Let's go walk on the
beach, look for a waterfall, chase some
rainbows. I'm here for you, Maui.
I'm celibate, though. So, it's got to be
like that
cuz you know, Maui, there's nasty things
out there you don't want to get. So,
especially the jardian. What What the
hell with these stupid drugs? You don't
want to have the swelling between the
Never mind. I watch too much TV and I
check out the the show Silo, you guys,
on Apple TV cuz I tell you what, they're
telling you what they're going to do.
So, you got to watch these shows and
take notes because it's called Silo, you
guys. Check it out. Holy [ __ ] Talk to
you later. Have a good one. Yeah, 911
was an inside job. And Charlie Kirk's
not dead. He's in Vajala. It's off the
coast of Australia.
>> What just happened in the last 7 seconds
of that set? She just utilized the last
10 seconds harder than I've seen you use
4 and 1/2 minutes. You [ __ ] Listen.
Learn from her. See, ladies and
gentlemen, give it a go for her. She's
celibate.
Or maybe if you proposition her
properly, she might sell a bit, you
know, maybe just a little bit. All
right, coming to the stage, ladies and
gentlemen. Comedy's baby of the year. I
I don't know if you'll ever escape that
term.
>> Especially cuz I found out your last
name actually means baby, right?
>> Oh, you're permanently. I don't I can't
wait till you're bald and old. I'm so
like baby of comedy. No, he's really a
young face. Ladies and gentlemen, again
for Jackson Bayine.
Gina's just jealous of my hair
>> every day.
>> All right, before we were doing
character night, but before I even do
that, like, dude, a lot of the the
characters you guys saw tonight was just
comedians
passing up as characters.
They were like, "Yeah, this is me, but
it's a character.
All right.
>> How's you doing, huh?
>> How you No, I'm not going to go that
Boston. I'm not going to start throwing
out slurs.
>> Yeah, she know.
>> You want me to?
>> Hey,
>> no, it's way more than that, guy. It's
so much more than that. I I grew up I
grew up with like we had like the more
blue collala you have your people the
more they drink, you know? Like I grew
up where like I was at I was at a dinina
at 9:00 in the morning on a Tuesday and
I heard I heard someone come up and ask
this very construction worker looking
guy if he wanted more coffee and he
goes, "Nah, it's time for me to it's
time for me to switch geese and buy some
bees."
I was like, "That's how I know where I'm
around some plumbers.
Like my my dad grew up as a as a
construction work in in New England.
>> And naturally, he's going to be
accidentally racist. You know, that's
how it works. You get you can't get one
without the other.
And he my my birthday falls around
Easter.
And
he we took me out he took me out to
lunch after after he dinner with my mom
cuz they were divorced. And the only
place open was a Chinese restaurant.
So we're there, we're ordering and then
he gets to what he's ordering and he
looks it straight in the face and he
goes,
"Can I get a puff rise?
I have to drop character for this part
because dude I was like, "Dad,
what are you doing?"
And he looked back at me just like
he was a dog that just pooped on the
rug. He was like, "I didn't mean to do
it. It just came out of my mouth.
He's not that bad, guys. He just worked
in construction." You know what I
saying, kid? All right. Whatever. You
don't like my dad. That's fine. He
he taught me how to make fun of people,
but it was at his mother's expense. And
she actually talked like this. Like she
was the one that I got a Crown Royal bag
from when I was a kid. Put all my toy.
You guys know a crown royal bag.
>> Yeah, exact. That's exactly what I had
in there.
No, she
he taught me how to make fun of people
at her expense.
At her expense.
He It was a pretty easy target.
Like she had that neck that like was
fused together so like she couldn't move
her head without her shoulders.
And she also had the elbows that didn't
leave her her ribs. So it just the whole
time,
but anytime I saw it coming around the
corner,
you just you didn't even need to see it.
You you could hear it.
You just see the the the [ __ ] the the
water shaking on the table and then she
would just come around the corner just
going.
She was a T-Rex, guys. She had the It's
okay. You can laugh at my grandmother.
She she had her own things. She thought
anybody that was gay had a shiny face. I
don't know how that makes any [ __ ]
sense.
And then my mom came out as gay years
later after she died. And she never even
thought she had a shiny face. She missed
the biggest one in front of her.
All right. I thought you guys laugh at
my mom or something, but I'm Jackson by
now. Good night.
Keep it going for Jackson Bayine, ladies
and gentlemen. His Boston accent. Keep
it going,
>> dude. The online chat right now. I've
never seen so many white people upset
about cultural appropriation.
That's the only time I've ever seen
white people complain about cultural
appropriation. It's like, "That's not a
Boston accent. What kind of a kick is
that?" That's hilarious. Don't go to
Boston, Jackson. Wait a couple months.
All right, coming to the stage. Uh, not
Jackson after he ate a Mario PowerUp
mushroom. This is a different person
altogether. Ladies and gentlemen, for
Shahane Nelson.
>> Hello, I'm Shane Nelson. I have a
three-legged dog.
Pretty good, huh, Joel? I'd say spot on,
dude. Denmark in the house. Are you
ladies from Denmark? Cuz that's what's
up.
>> Here's my impression of a girl from
Denmark. Yes. Woo.
Not
>> spot on, dude.
I uh my family's from Minnesota. My
dad's from Minnesota. And the other day
I was uh I live in Kihei. I was taking a
shower and there was a giant spider in
my shower. Does anyone else here have a
giant spider in my shower?
>> Dude, it was so big and scary. I
actually called my dad. I'm 34 years
old. And I called my dad. I was like,
"Dad, there's a big scary spider in my
bathroom." And my dad said, "Well,
you're uh you're 34 years old and I'm in
Minnesota, so you're on your own, bud."
I was like, "Dad, I'm super scared. What
should I do?" And my dad said, "Well,
here's my rule. If the spider has a web,
I let it live. If it's a freerange
spider, you kill it.
>> I was like, "Got it. Kill the homeless
ones."
Right.
I uh
my dad, he tries to live through me all
the time. He asks me questions about the
dating world. My dad's been married to
my mom for 40 years, so he hasn't dated
in a minute besides my mom. So, he'll
ask me questions about dating. I had to
tell my dad. I'm like, "Dad, dude, my
man, things are different." Like,
remember back in the day when it was an
insult for someone to call you a
buttlicker? Like on the playground in
the '9s, calling someone a buttlicker
was an insult.
Nowadays, people are proud buttlickers.
The kids call it eating ass.
When I told my dad, he couldn't believe
it. My dad's like, "Oh, really? You're
out there licking butts, huh?"
I was like, "Yeah, we're licking butts,
dude." And my dad said, "Well, do you
take girls on dates or you just out
there licking butts?"
And I said, "We can't go on dates,
dude." Because let's say we go for sushi
and an hour later I'm licking her butt,
eating sushi and licking butt. That's
how you get Sam Manila.
>> I can tell you're all looking at me like
I'm a buttlicker.
>> Never lick a butt, dude. Scouts honor.
Never licked a butt.
But I've been this close. I was right
there, dude. I was right there and I was
looking at it and it was looking back at
me and I thought to myself, "You're
cute, but I don't know." So, I decided
to blow on it. You know, just a little.
And what I expected to happen, have you
guys ever blown into a cat's face? You
ever in a cat's face?
They'll put their ears back and they're
like, "Get away from me."
That's what I expected to happen. That's
not what happened. It blew back
and it sounded like this
solo,
>> dude. Impression night. Jabba the butt.
Are you kidding me?
>> Standing ovation. First standing ovation
of the night. Gino. Mark it. Mark it.
Remember this moment, everyone. This was
the height of my life.
Do you guys remember that cereal? The
the blueberries. You guys remember
Booberries?
>> Spooky, right? Oops, all blueberries.
They had like a Dracula like guy. He's
like, "Oh, all blueberries. Oh, boo."
You guys remember that?
>> Halloween.
>> What's that?
>> For Halloween.
>> Yes, for Halloween. It was a cereal. And
I'd like to say every time I think about
that commercial and that cereal, I
always think of our friend Danny, who
you're still here, so I'm saying this
joke. Danny always makes me think of
blueberries because I think he's a
serial killer.
Said it with love. I just got moved up
the list. That's okay though. That's
okay. Um I do smoke weed here and there.
Like here and there. I'm smoking weed
everywhere. I smoke weed with goats on
boats. I smoke weed in parades on
floats. I smoke weed near and far. I
just smoked some weed in my car and I'll
smoke more weed when I leave this bar. I
smoke weed in blunts and bongs. I smoke
weed with [ __ ] and thongs. I smoke weed
on planes and trains. I smoke weed in
Mir Shains. My name is Shane Nelson and
good night.
>> Keep it going for Shane Nelson, ladies
and gentlemen.
Dressed like he wants to show you the
biggest crystal on Maui. What's up with
that outfit? That's a
That's a wild one, man. I thought that
was the character. Then he didn't
address it at all. I'm like, I think
that's just him. [ __ ] All right. Uh, so
we got we we got a a couple on the list
I want to check out real quick. Uh,
Peter, where are you at, Peter? Oh,
okay. You'll be next next. Not next, but
next next. And then followed by that,
David. Uh, how are you on plain time? Do
you need to go up right now? You're
good. Okay. So, you're up in up in two
more. And then, uh, where's Abby? Abby,
you ready?
Abby. Abby. Rose calling once.
>> Calling twice. All right, Peter, you
ready for now?
>> Gotcha.
>> Peter, are you ready?
>> He's doing a quick change into his
costume. I don't know if he's got a last
name. He might have an accent. He's
definitely got sunglasses at night. It's
one of those people. Ladies and
gentlemen, get up for Peter.
>> Super. My name is Peter.
That is correct. Oh, look. I do love all
of you. You're looking so sexy.
Oh, unlike another Austrian, I am a
successful artist.
One fella got it. That's correct. Ah,
>> art is great. Do we have any more
artists here?
>> Yeah. K. Yeah. Boss Marku, what do you
make?
your dance moves. Oh, yeah. Getting the
jiggy and down with it. Yeah. Too bad no
one else can see you.
>> It's okay. That was good.
I don't know. Do we have some people
with addictions in here?
>> That's a lot of you. Okay. Mr. Tank Top,
what is your addiction?
>> Acid.
>> Acid. Oh, yeah. Yeah. So, your brain is
melted. Huh?
>> Are you tripping now?
>> This is no accent.
>> He's not French. Oh, gone. We have
addiction. You know, porn addiction.
All right.
Oh, yeah. I can't stop making it.
>> That's right. That's right. All right.
Do we have any more? Only fans people
here.
>> Hello lady. Yes. So what is your version
of the art?
>> Mine is mostly Hansel unretle porn.
It consists of a lot of hiking.
Is there any collaborators here who
wants to go hiking?
You do get candy at the end.
as a [ __ ] She helps us. She is not so
bad.
>> S is minus sister Gretle. Yeah,
>> I love her so so much. It's more of a
Game of Thrones sisterhood.
It's a twin.
So that's a dragon. Yeah, of course
there's a dragon.
He's spitz.
Okay, let's see here.
Mr. Hoodie,
>> do you have one or two pairs of assless
chaps?
>> How many? One or two?
You have You have nine. You have no
assless chaps. That is so sad. Pity this
man.
>> Chino, how many do you have?
>> Two. That is correct answer. That's
right.
It's more of a garter belt system.
Just only cuffs around the ankles. It's
mostly chap.
>> I don't know.
>> It's nice to see me. Thank you very
much.
>> Are you coming or going?
You're here.
>> You're here right now, but you're going
there.
Where are you running off to?
>> She She cut away. [ __ ] It's hard to
catch women these days.
I know it is.
I have an iPhone,
but I know our government is spying on
us, so it's more of a paranoid Android.
That was stupid. It's okay.
All of it. It's all stupid. Stupid.
There's so much on the internet. How
do How many of you spend more than four
hours on social media each day?
That is one truthful person. Two
truthful people. That's right. There's
so much crazy stuff out there. That is
why I am I I think we are too too hard
on God.
We are very hard. Imagine being
omnipotent or omnipresent. That is like
watching every stupid YouTube video on
Tik Tok, on Instagram, on everything all
at once for all time. So make good
content.
God likes Hansel and Gretle porn. All
right. My name is Peter. I have a
shinier.
Check out his only
>> Peter.
>> It's Peter. Okay. Sorry, I mispronounced
your name. I was using American English.
That's my fault. Uh, it's so funny that
Denmark people were so wholly
unconcerned with your German accent.
They're just like,
>> "Yeah, we hear that. That's not that
funny. I don't understand why that's
funny." Um, all right. So, coming to the
stage, David, you ready? Ladies and
gentlemen, your next performer has got a
plane to catch. Let's get him up on
stage before he's got to go. Mr. David
Ames.
I was supposed to be the headliner,
but when I saw the chair of the red
chair instead of the standard comedian's
stool
and no steaming hot white towel. wall
>> so I could put my what do you call that
with your red
umbrella Hawaiian drink. I'm from
Hollywood. Okay,
Mr. Promoter.
And when I come a long way to do a
comedy show, I expect to be treated with
respect.
>> I'm really upset.
I'm so upset.
>> [ __ ] I forgot my entire act.
But I'm a professional.
I'm from Hollywood
as uh
you know what? But I think I got to
I think I got to fire my agent.
And now I'm stuck here.
I think I need a new agent.
Mr. Promoter, uh, you looking for a new
agent? I need somebody from, uh, new
comic to, uh, you know, get gigs for.
>> I didn't mean what I said before.
So, as you all may know me, David Ames
from Hollywood about that I do comedy
and I'm quite funny.
>> I also uh was in the movies.
>> I was an actor in the movies. I was in
this movie called Catwoman. Has anybody
seen Catwoman?
>> Yeah. Only 23 years old.
>> I was in that movie. You recognize me
from the movie?
>> No. Come on.
You know when Catwoman, she's chasing uh
she's chasing the uh you know the bad
guy, you know, through the amusement
park and stuff. Remember that scene?
>> Okay. Well, it's a big crowd of people.
Well, I'm in that crowd, right? And when
you comes around, the crowd has to
disperse. And that was me.
It's okay. You guys don't have to watch
the whole movie to to see, you know, me
in that movie.
You can get online and you can just now
you know the scene to check right
and then you can go and say I remember
that guy that's the guy
who was really upset
when he and did comedy in Maui
and you can look at it over and over
again.
What kind of movies you guys make here?
Surfing movies.
My feet are all muddy.
My feet are all muddy. My private
personal professional.
So I thought helicopter pilot was trying
to get me onto this rock.
I don't know. Maybe he didn't like my
attitude or something, but ended up
landing me on this. What was it? Ki
Kawaii. I don't know.
So anyway, now I don't have a helicopter
pilot to take me back to Hollywood. So,
>> hey, you're not filming this, are you?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You're filming this? I didn't say you
could film my set. I'm from Hollywood. I
get permission for that kind of thing.
I'm going to call my Hollywood lawyer.
>> He's an actor. Keep it going for David,
ladies and gentlemen. And if you come to
this show and you want me to book for
you and you see this room and you still
want me to book for you, you're probably
not as talented as you think. That's how
that this is this is a golden room.
Right. Right. All right. Uh if you
didn't if you didn't like his comedy,
check out his IMDb. Uh you can see him
in various projects such as Catwoman.
Was that the Halle Berry Catwoman?
>> Okay. Okay. I think it was the Halib
Berry Catwoman. Uh, if you don't
remember Holly Berry, she's beautiful.
Never mind. All right.
It's been a while. All right, ladies and
gentlemen, the moderator of our comment
section is gonna be joining us on stage.
Uh, if you don't know why his job is so
difficult, check out our YouTube channel
as this is live streaming. It is. If you
think you guys are a rough crowd, huh,
not even close. They are so mean to us.
Check it out. Comedy simulator. It's
going right now. I'm walk around with
the tip bucket while I give it up for
the next comic. Ladies and gentlemen,
Jimbo.
Let's keep it going for Chino, the
infamous leader of this fever dream that
he doesn't have to do. He doesn't have
to do this. He doesn't. Uh, it's like
community service. All right. My
character, I've been working very hard
at this. Uh, my character is going to be
a overweight 36-year-old depressed
nitrous addict that just got booked on
his fourth gig in four years this
Sunday. So, he needs to work out some
material.
Stick with me.
Pretty poor right now. I'm so poor. I
had to do that terrible, terrible thing
called the gun trade in. I did it. They
hosted here on Maui. The cops hosted a
gun tradein. And I went and I turned in
one of my guns and they gave me a $100
gift card to Foodland.
And I walked away thinking, "Well,
that's a [ __ ] deal. I could have got way
more than $100 if I just went into
Foodland with my gun."
I asked them if they could reverse it.
They're like, "No."
Um, man, any online shoppers out there?
>> This is a room full of very interactive
people. Any people out there?
>> Who likes air?
>> Drugs,
>> cheap drugs. If you were going to do
drugs from like a thrift store of drugs,
like a secondhand drug market, what drug
would you be comfortable doing?
>> She said measculine.
>> Hell yeah.
I don't even know how to spell
measculine.
>> What's the C?
of course mystery knows how to spell me
masculine. He's got a tatted on him,
too.
Um,
let me see. Where was I going before
masculine
places?
Um, let's see.
Let me work out.
I grew up in the '9s where uh I don't
know if it like you, but my mom, she's a
good mom. She told me, she said, "Jimmy,
you have to be nice to the nerds. You
have to be nice to them because they
couldn't end up owning the company you
work for. Anyone else's mom say that to
them? Yeah. And no one else had parents
that didn't believe in them enough to
say they would own the company. These
nerds could own the company you work
for. You got to be nice to them. But it
worked. I'm super nice to all the nerds.
>> I can't imagine parents these days have
to give the same message and just be
like, "Hey, you have to be nice to nerds
because they could end up owning
>> a gun.
All right, I know you can't see it, but
three people chuckled on that. All
right, so the average for tonight,
that's above average. All right,
>> I'm doing good.
>> I can't have kids these days. I can't um
having kids on the brink of the water
wars seems kind of irresponsible.
I'm really fat and slow. Like, having a
kid, you know how slow they run?
>> They would slow me down worse. Plus,
they can't even hold a gun properly till
they're taught in fourth grade in
America.
That's backto-back school shooter jokes.
>> It's better than backto-back school
shootings. Am I right?
>> That guy said, "Yep,
this feels like a school shooting
without all the bullets. Just a bunch of
fear and hiding under tables hoping no
one looks at you.
Terrible."
I don't know. My mom stopped asking me
if I was going to have kids. She used to
ask me all the time. I guess you don't
know the good times when you're in them,
right? No.
>> She's like, she just knows I can't
anymore.
>> It's not getting better.
>> Oh, yeah. Online shopping.
>> I [ __ ] hate online shopping. I really
do. Because there's that new option
called pay later. You guys seen that
[ __ ] Pay later. the audacity of these
[ __ ] to think that if I can't
pay now,
>> things are going to get better
and I'm going to be able to pay later.
Like, this is already later. This is on
credit. You want me to pay later than
credit?
Deal. Every time.
Fall for it every [ __ ] time. I'm so
poor. I have Amazon light. Anyone know
what that is?
Oh, you have money in here. Okay. Eating
basil steak. I see. Amazon light is $3 a
month. Same exact thing as Amazon Prime,
but I can never check out.
They know it's going to decline. They
just saving their processing fees. All
right, let's see. I'll end you guys with
one more.
I um Anyone in here watch porn?
Ma'am, we know you do. We we watched you
walk in. We saw that stride. I was like,
"That lady watches porn."
I do think the porn industry needs to be
studied. It's not how she studies it,
but like it does need to be studied
because somehow porn dodged the epidemic
that is advertisements.
Like, don't get me wrong, there's ads in
porn, but it's just more porn.
You're like watching you're like, "Oh,
>> a different angle of that anal."
And for me with someone like me with
ADD, that's terrible cuz I don't know
which one I'm going to finish to now.
>> I don't even hit the X. It's like P and
P in porn.
>> All right, that's my porn joke. I'm
Jimbo. I love you, chat. Even though
you're all incelss and you have a short
attention span and you're mean and I
love you.
Keep it going for Jimbo, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> We know when we see a male porn star
chug a Coca-Cola at the end of a scene
that he's prophesized what's to come.
Just like American Idol. All right,
ladies and gentlemen, coming back on
stage. Three weeks in a row now, right?
Coming back for a third set in a row.
Ladies and gentlemen, again for Sasha.
>> Hello.
Oh, you stole all my porn jokes, Jimbo.
That was what I was going to leave with.
Uh, but so it's character night. I
always do a character. It's called
masking. Um, if you don't know what that
is, look it up. It might also be a weird
sex thing. I don't really know. Uh, but
that's not what I meant by that. Uh,
speaking of weird sex things, anybody
here single?
>> Anybody? Yeah, there you go. Yeah. Are
you on the apps?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah, I'm on the apps.
Uh, you know, since the pandemic, it
seems like the only reasonable way to
meet people. Uh, but one of the things
I'm running into a lot is people who are
ENM, ethical non- monogamy.
Yeah. You familiar? Yeah.
>> So,
yeah. So, you know, I dipped my toe into
polyamory, ethical nominogamy. Um, if
you ever heard the expression like too
many cooks in the kitchen, like apply
that to your relationship and that's
what polyamory
basically is. So, you know, I had two
boyfriends and one of my boyfriends also
had three girlfriends and it was just a
situation where someone was always
pissed off at somebody else and it was
not on my end. Like my So, one of my
boyfriends, he lived out of state and he
was a cuckled. Like that's a whole other
sex thing. If you're not familiar,
that's that's somebody who like is turn
Yeah. Yeah. Somebody who's turned on by
you being with other people. Like I miss
that ex. He He was actually one of my
few exes that I really miss. Uh but but
the other one had two other girlfriends
and and this is always a thing with
polyamory. There's always people who say
they're cool with it who are not cool
with it. So his two other girlfriends
were not cool with it. I was cool with
it. Those two were not cool with it. And
I mean the thing is when I got into it,
I was like I actually liked his other
girlfriends that they're cool. Um, but
it was it was a thing where they were
always like pissed off about something.
And so, you know, I was at work and I
get this text where I'm like, "Oh, you
know, she's mad cuz like she found your
hair like wrapped around my dick." Uh,
yeah. Cuz I'm a shedddter. I've got a
lot of hair if you haven't noticed. Uh,
which is not my fault. Um, and this is
just such an unreasonable text to be
getting at work in like in your 30s or
really at any age. It's just a stupid
stupid thing. And it's like I I don't
know what I'm supposed to do about that.
It's like dude, clean your dick better.
I don't know. I don't know what to say
about that. And so then the other
girlfriend
uh I don't know, got pissed when we all
went to the Renfair together cuz he was
hanging out with me more than with her.
Um I mean if you want to see like a vin
diagram of like people who are into
renfares and people who are polyamorous
and then you you see in the middle is
this big section of people having
awkward fights the renfair that that is
absolutely a thing. So yeah I I in the
end I just decided that polyory was not
really a thing for me but you know so
back on the apps. So, let me ask you
something since you're on the apps.
Like, do when you give a num your number
to a woman, does she ever like
immediately send a picture of like her
tits or her [ __ ]
>> No. No. Okay. So, that's that's more
like a woman thing, I guess. Like, you
know, when you give your number to a
guy, he immediately sends a picture of
his dick. Um, which I'm actually not
complaining about as a mostly straight
woman. Like, I I don't mind that. It's
not terrible. Um,
uh, so yeah, I've just mostly been
getting a lot of like, you know, good
dickpicks. Not terrible. I I do kind of
wonder what what what would happen if
women just started doing that to men?
They probably like it, I guess. Would
anybody like that?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Um, I mean,
that's how we'll know that we're really
reached equality is, you know, when
we're just harassing in with pictures of
our our tits and our [ __ ] Um,
yeah. Um, so anyway, yeah, I now just
basically in a sexing relationship with
a guy on the other side of the world and
it's all me sending pictures of my tits
and him sending pictures of his dick and
it's the healthiest relationship I've
ever been in. So, I'm really happy for
me. Thank you.
Give it up over Sasha, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> And just remember, you have three
attempts to hack her iCloud password,
you weirdos. Don't do it. All right,
>> man. You guys have been just pulling
teeth tonight. What's going on here?
Huh?
>> Did everybody just like get broken up
via text message tonight? What's going
on, you guys? Why are you guys so sad?
What happened? What happened?
>> By the way, Tamua's filmer was in here
in the audience tonight. You guys know
local comic sensation Tamua? Yeah. His
uh his videographer was in the audience
tonight. And he's going to go back and
tell Tamua how bad it was. Oh my god. Oh
my god. My reputation's ruined. You guys
all just ruined me. You sons of [ __ ]
You bankrupt me. I love you all. All
right, ladies and gentlemen, coming up
to the stage, a first timer for us. He's
got a a stand for music and ukulele. I
have no idea what's about to happen.
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up for
Juan Maritime.
>> Well, I do have I do have a character
for you. It is uh Johnny Cash in his
punk phase.
>> A lot of people don't know Johnny Cash
was the first punk. You might think of
Sid Vicious, you probably think of
Johnny Rotten, but let me tell you, it
was Johnny Cash.
But, uh, he came in, I'm sorry, I
screwed this up already.
This is Johnny Cash about the era where
he came in off of looking at his career
over the ass end of a mule in Das,
Arkansas, and he saw June Carter Cash,
who was country western royalty, and he
made several passes at her
unsuccessfully.
And uh so this is the prelude to the
famous song I walk the line.
Remember this one.
So there's a little infidelity that's
inspired this original rough draft of I
walk the line. I keep a close watch on
this heart of mine.
I keep my eyes wide open all the time.
I keep the ends out for the tile that
bind.
But she was fine,
so I crossed the line.
She was fine,
so I cross the line.
I find it very, very easy to be true. I
find myself alone when each day is
through. Yes, I'll admit I was a fool to
cheat on you. But she was fine, so I
cross the line. As sure as night is dark
and day is light. I find you on my mind
sometimes at night.
And the happiness I found proves I was
right cuz she's so fine. I cross the
line. Yes, she was fine. So I cross the
line. I find it very very easy to be
true.
But the question is to be true to whom?
Cuz I ain't got no one to be true to.
And that's just fine. I cross the line.
As sure as day is dark and night is
light.
Hey, wait. I don't think I said that
right.
I way. I'm flying high tonight.
I'm feeling fine. I'm across the line.
I'm feeling fine. I'm across the line. I
find it very, very hard to hit these
notes, but that's the way these low down
notes is wrote. I'm going to need a
little something to wet my throat.
Please pass that medicinal lady proof
antidote
and I'll sing fine.
If I recall the line
and I'll sing fine if I recall the line.
I do not think it very likely I'll
forget
that Johnny Cash is the guy who wrote
this hit. Oh, sure. I [ __ ] it up a
little bit, but Johnny be fine.
He's across the line.
Yeah, Johnny be fine.
>> One maritime, ladies and gentlemen. Keep
it going for him.
What?
one maritime. That's a water wine. A
water wine. Um,
>> you know, I don't want to like Thank you
for sharing that with us. Um, I don't
want to say anything
at your expense for the purposes of
comedy. However, I would like to read my
favorite comments
from the online.
Somebody said, uh, dance dancy Steve
called you Johnny short on cash. I
thought that was cute.
>> Uh, toxic Rick said, "I thought I seen
that name somewhere. He's on the Epstein
list."
>> Oh god, these people are terrible. Uh,
what else? SP2P99
just said Dr. Fouchy. I
>> I think he thinks you look like Dr.
Fouchy. I don't He just said Dr. Fouchy.
Yeah,
>> I I understand. Yeah, it's I'm pretty
sure it's the same guy that just calls
me Blazian. Uh
>> I'm not black, but I take the compliment
regardless. All right, we got two more
comics we're going to call tonight.
>> Yeah,
>> you called in advance. He's got all
types of stuff ready for character
night. I'm curious to see what it is.
Ladies and gentlemen, put your hands
together for Tyson.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you, brother.
Huh? You know, it was really hard
getting here. My [ __ ] bike, I
couldn't get the seat on the wheel at
the last minute. [ __ ]
I had to call the ride. We don't want
your house. [ __ ] nobody will bring
you a Uber. But got some puli [ __ ]
smoke and uh you know my spirit animals.
A gorilla [ __ ] silverback. I don't
know. I don't know.
My spirit animal is gorilla and uh
wizzy. I am the dizzy.
>> Well, that's such a big donkey dink. But
anyways, my name is Lincoln. Some people
over in private, they call me stinking
Lincoln. Um they think I'm just another
stinky dippy. But I got plans. I got
dreams, too. You know, one of these days
I'll I'll raise myself up out of this um
place of uh hitchhikers. I actually
stuck some on my leg for a fact, but
they fell off cuz they weren't ripe yet.
But you know what a hitchhiker is? It's
not that [ __ ] clown that wants to
ride the hik. It is the [ __ ] that gets
on your socks and on your pants. It's
like little barbery [ __ ] Anyways,
enough of factual stuff. You know, my
feelings been hurt out there on the um
on the open plains of uh free camping at
the beach. You know, it's not always
easy and sometimes it's just like most
of the hippies over here in the pucker.
Intense.
Anyways, uh that's a pun if you guys
never heard of one. They're pretty good
in the kitchen. Um yeah, I heard all of
them back in jail, but that was another
lifetime ago. Right now I'm I'm
concerned about my safety. You know
what's love got to do with it? Um the
kind of turn. But yeah, man. I got my um
non-metal knife. That way if buggers
step to me um I'm ready.
But um you know they're not going to
catch me with slivers of uh German metal
on there. Wow. Rough crowd tonight. No
snikes. Yeah. Anyway, uh yeah, I heard
this high spice is pretty good. If you
can't feel your PKA, you just put a
little of that on there.
That'll wake you up for a couple days.
Better than that ice [ __ ] they say
stalling down the guls.
Anyway, yeah, don't make many jokes
about that. Those guys stay up all
night, do you? And
anyway,
>> I know I get a [ __ ] laugh one way or
another. Um,
>> you know, so I had a date the other
night and um,
>> somebody's supposed to say what was his
name.
>> What was his name?
>> Oh, Neil or Bob. I can't [ __ ] my
memories. My brain is kind of mushed. I
don't know. But I want to tell you guys
about my fanny pack a little bit. Um, I
just I fought hard for this one in the
third world war um online. But uh, yeah.
Uh, here's my little golden rope.
Sometimes I play like I'm getting
through the VIP.
Um, oh yeah, and song about it. Yeah, I
wrote it.
>> I'm stinking Lincoln from Pyia.
You can smoke me from here.
[ __ ] you. I'm not I'm just a lover. I'm
not a fighter. But I did. I mean, I
literally got my ass kicked at a gas
station last week. This [ __ ] want to
crank me, but I had one cooler in my
hand and I turned around and I was
cranking the cooler at the same time. He
literally raised his right foot and
kicked my ass. I still did a little
bruise, I guess. I mean, I hope he never
broke his [ __ ] ankle. Well, I do hope
he did. But um yeah, I finally literally
after all the fights I've been in from
first grade to [ __ ] six months ago,
got my ass kicked. Sure did. That goes
out to my friend over there from New
Hampshire. I'm a maniac from way back.
And if you think my accent ain't real.
Get offline. Come on the [ __ ] plane.
I'll pick you up. I'll put a lay on you
and then we'll [ __ ] put you in the
sugarcane field. So seriously, that goes
out to my brother over there from New
Hampshire. I heard he was taking a
[ __ ] blood bath on the internet. You
guys are all [ __ ] funny standups when
it comes to sitting in your underwear
with your dank in your hand and [ __ ]
one finger typing. Anyways, that's all I
got to say about that. You guys want to
beat me up? I'm Tyson on there. But hold
on, hold on.
>> Hold on. I got my man wipes.
>> Yeah.
>> And you know because when you're in the
bucket brush, you never you don't want
to use [ __ ] kind three leaves. Oh.
Uh, you know, usually my my uh what do
they call that? Your footprint is pretty
good, but I got some Andes chips.
>> And then, uh, I'm kind of known as the
tea man. A pa. I give out tea bags.
There you go. You look like a willing
guy for teaagging it.
>> All right. Thanks a lot, guys.
>> Keep going, Tyson, ladies and gentlemen.
>> Hey, I just got a really good idea for a
character.
a guy that shows up to the pawn shop.
>> Oh, wow. What's going on here?
>> Yeah, dude. These two need to meet. I
love this. Yeah. Hey guys, that's a
future episode of America's Most Wanted
if I've ever seen one. That's a That'll
be an unsolved mystery in 48 hours for
sure. Oh man. No, the idea is a
crackhead that goes to the pawn shop
with a bunch of stuff, but it actually
is super rare and valuable. He's like,
"No, I got this rare rock from the
1700s." It's actually that is that is a
rare brick. Um all right, last comic of
the night. Wow, you guys have been here.
Uh
what a great room this could have been.
If we'd just given you enough drugs as
him, right? If only if only we had
enough for this entire room. You guys
would have been the best audience. We
would have had a bouncy castle. You guys
would have been great. But you guys have
been fine. Did you guys have a good time
tonight?
That's the most sound you've made
tonight. Thank you for that. I
appreciate you. Make the most noise so
now's noise you can cuz you got your
last performer coming up now. Get up for
Eddie V.
Johnny short on cash inspired me. So I
want to do a John. It's character night.
Give it up for character night.
>> Hell yeah. I love this [ __ ] This is how
we find new stuff. New [ __ ] to talk
about.
This was This is Johnny Cash as recorded
by Trent Resner.
>> I hurt myself today.
I focus on the pain. The only thing
that's real,
right?
Uh this is my cousin at the Poke Counter
Food Land. Kihei.
>> Hi. How you doing today? Yep. You You
got What do you recommend?
Step to the right. No pokey for you.
He's the pokey Nazi, in case you don't
know.
Um,
this is Does anybody remember All in the
Family? Those were the days.
Is anybody It's probably too old
reference, but I'm going to do it
anyway.
>> Ain't it? When's that useless meathead
going to get a going to get a job? Oh,
Aie. He He's He's got an interview
tomorrow.
I got some laughs from outside of the
building. That's amazing. Wow. I'll take
it. Um, this is this is okay for has
anybody been to the Hilo airport?
>> Yeah. So, it can qualify as the world's
mustiest
smells like mold airport in the world.
>> It was that way 20 years ago and it's
still exactly that way. It's amazing.
Um, character night. Character night.
Okay. Uh, this is a guy, you know, from
back east. It's a wicked pisser. Oh, or
a guy from Brooklyn, he's like, "Never
forget." Now, now it's like, "Forget
about it." Now it's like, "Never forget
about it." Right.
>> Um, character night. Th This is This is
cool. Like, so Scoobs, I should I sure
could go for one of those Scooby snacks.
Ah, movies.
Um, what do we got? Oh, character night.
Okay.
Nah. What's up, Doc?
Uh, I'm going to blow the Earth up. It
obstructs my view of Venus.
What? The Earth creature after him. He
has stolen the B33 burillium C space
modulator.
>> Anybody remember that?
>> All right, I got one clap. That's
something. You know, at this hour, you
know, everybody's been been drained.
Okay, so um we got we got, you know,
character night. This is great. You
know, I love it. I love it. Oh, uh this
is this is character night. We're we're
doing Callahan Welsh.
That was pretty good, right?
>> Oh, I got one for you. Danny Salazar.
>> Hey, ladies. I just got paid.
>> I'm I'm I'm in case you don't know, I'm
I'm drunk. I'm alcoholic. I'm Danny the
alcoholic
cow killer. And I'm willing to spend my
check to get some wild last to [ __ ] me.
I don't know if anybody didn't see that
night. That was good. Um character
night. I love it. Um,
RFK.
Um, let's see. Uh,
Bernie Sanders.
Bernie. Bernie Sanders. Uh, is this a
Okay.
Um, one one last one here. Um,
Chewy
>> getting rejected again on all the dating
apps.
>> I'm Eddie V.
>> Keep it.
>> Sorry, Chewy. Girls don't like back
hair. Keep it going for Eddie V, ladies
and gentlemen, and all the comics you
guys heard tonight.
money.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Hand sanitizer.
>> Thank you. Hand sanitizer. That's a
thing. Uh we're still using these.
Totally. Uh Trish's going to walk around
with the tip bucket one more time
because you gave me $8 and two
lollipops. That's not enough. That's not
enough for beer. Uh she's going to do
one more lap. If you're feeling
generous, appreciate it. If you don't,
that's fine, too. Guys, some nights of
comedy are easy and some nights are
hard. I'm not going to lie. Tonight was
difficult for all the comics. They all
did their best to make you laugh. Uh,
thank you so much for being here and
being a part of the show. Uh, we're
sorry if we didn't meet your standards
by any means, but also at the same time,
nobody charged you. So, if you had a
good time, tell your friends. And if you
didn't, just shut your [ __ ] mouth cuz
it's a small island and we don't need
rumors, right? Just tell them it was
good. Tell them you had a great time.
No. Uh, next week we'll do better. uh or
not and it'll get progressively worse
and worse and then that's what the show
will become. We're willing to ride this
train to hell. We don't care where you
hopped on.
>> We are going to one destination, one
destination alone. Uh I haven't thought
of a theme for next week. Does anybody
want to come up with a theme for next
week right now? Anybody got ideas?
>> A theme for comedy next week.
>> Cringe comedy.
>> What was that?
>> Cringe comedy. That's every week. Eddie
B, have you been missing all the
episodes? Every week has been as high
level of cringe.
>> What' you say?
>> Jane saw Bob. Unfortunately, too narrow.
Although I do appreciate it.
>> Kevin Smith. Okay, that's an idea.
That's an idea.
>> Outdated perspectives.
>> Outdated perspect No, that's a tough
one. We can't do outdated perspectives.
Uh, that'll be a lot of slurs and
epithets.
>> What was that?
>> Your wife [ __ ] on your day. That That's
a whole cat. or like a take my wife no
to take her type day or would you joke
>> drunk?
>> Drunks.
>> Yeah, drunk uncle.
>> Oh, I kind of like drunkles. What do you
guys think? Drunks.
>> We're talking about drunk family members
next week.
>> There it is. There it is. Next week's
theme is drunk family members. Thank
you. Thank you, friend. Drunkles and
above. Next week, traumatized by drunk
family members. All right, we'll see you
next week, guys. Don't forget to tip
your bar staff. Give it up everybody
coffee and bar for doing such a great
job tonight.
Danny London kes fantastic human beings.
>> Take great care. Thank you so much. I'm
Chino.
>> I hope you had a good night. Give it up
for Skyler from Shrewcat Studios doing
the the videoing. We love you guys.
We'll see you next week. Uh I'm going to
do a quick little interview with these
uh online peeps and then we're going to
call it a night. So, thank you so much
for joining us. End simulation
for now. See you next week. Love you.
Bye.
Bam. There I am. What's up, guys?
>> Thank you so much for watching. Oh,
thank you, Radio Star. Appreciate you.
Always nice. Always nice words. Shout
out to me and Jimbo. I'll make sure he
hears it.
>> Jimbo is getting shouted. Where you at,
Jimbo?
guys. Thank you. Hey, I'll be honest
with you. Some Mondays we have a little
bit of we we bring as much energ as we
can. Uh, tonight was rough. We did our
best. Um, this was a rough night. Thank
you, Allison, for appreciating and
noticing. Um, also, you made a really
funny comment earlier. I can't remember
what it was, but I appreciate it. I saw
it. Um, thank you so much for watching
and sticking through this entire show,
you guys. That was a tough one. Oh,
wait. I got to give audience member of
the night some sauces. I'll be right
back.
Oh, here we go.
like
>> table.
>> All right. All right, I gave the hot
sauces out. I did I did my my my
husbandly duty. No, I was just joking.
Uh, what we got here? Despite what some
of you are saying,
sorry, I'm trying to catch up on the
comments cuz I was gone.
Yeah, Jim. Jimbo, give it up for Jimbo,
dude. Great moderator. Uh, he doesn't
boot you if you're being vocal. You
know, he listens to your feedback. He
only boots you if you really say
horrible horrible things. Um, look at
the Lowski pay his bill here. Go for it.
Look. Yeah.
I'll give you guys. You guys want to
see? I'll show you. I'll tell you. Say
hi, Ally. Right on. Good to see Ally,
one of our Maui peach.
>> What a great community member Labowski
me is. You know, every every community
needs a dude. I couldn't agree more. Um,
amateur comics in their natural habitat.
Yeah. uh this kind of so much. Um
normally there's more drugs involved,
but it's pretty close.
Jimbo does let the comedy fly, man. He
don't care. I appreciate it. He's uh
headlining his old hometown on the
mainland coming up soon, so follow him
on social media if you want to see
what's coming out.
Yeah, Jimbo is he is the people's comic.
Uh and hit or miss, he really does care,
you know. He really does want you guys
to be entertained. So, appreciate you.
Candy Jack, welcome back. Hey, thanks
for joining us in the chat again, too.
The guy in the tie-dye shirt just
pickpocketed me. Hey, you know what?
That's fine. Take take my [ __ ] I don't
have much. And uh I mean, look at what
he did with he had with what he had. He
could probably do more with what I have.
So, um racism question mark. Um maybe
not for me to say. Uh I don't know how
to answer that one. GXD cards. Uh
racism. Uh it's very possible. Um, no,
he shouldn't do comedy, but he's good at
letting Jo go. Hey, you know, we're all
learning to do comedy, whether you've
been doing it for years or minutes,
months, whatever. Um, yeah, he's saying
that I'm his mentor. Uh, I guess I'm
responsible for that. Uh, which just I
it's just, you know, a chain of unfunny
people. Um, who did Jimbo learn to not
be funny from? Me. And, uh, I learned to
not be funny from other comics as well.
What's up, Tyson? I don't know.
>> Cuz you Cuz I called it in.
>> What was that?
>> You got a five. Either three
>> for For what?
>> I'll give you three.
>> Sure.
>> For past, present, and future.
>> Past, present, and future dollars.
>> I do it.
>> Races.
>> Thank you. Appreciate you.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you from Tyson. Hey, babe. Tyson,
say what's up to the people.
>> Hey guys, thanks out there in the good
old video YouTube TV land.
>> And you thought he was pickpocketing me,
but he just didn't put money in my
pocket.
>> I picked him out of his pocket. I picked
his pocket. Some [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Hey, pick this. Look. Oh, I went another
Oh, we got
>> We got it again.
>> What is it?
>> Yes.
>> Ladies and gentlemen,
>> the one and only wearing a Dragon Ball Z
wig. We love her. Android 60. Um, where
is this located? We are at Pa Bay Coffee
and Bar on the island of Maui. We start
every Monday at 7:15 on the dot. Yeah,
right. He gave me his last thought. Hey,
you know what?
They smell like drugs. That's good
money.
Cuz at at this time, ones either smell
like drugs or they smell like butthole
and I'll take the drugs. Um at this age
in my 20s, I'd sniff a a dirty one. A
Ching Chang. Love your karate group.
Ching. Oh, that was the racism attempt.
Oh, got it. Nice try. Um, dude, yeah,
you can't beat my own family. I mean, I
my grandpa is probably one of the most
racist on the on my white side was
probably one of the most racist people.
He bought my uh my mom a microwave for a
child birth present and then when they
saw how Asian I was like, "Hey, so the
baby and nuke the [ __ ] and that was our
family joke." Yeah, dude. So, like
that's the family I come from. You think
you're going to hurt my feelings with
like, "Oh, me Chinese jokes?" Yeah, good
luck. Uh, yeah. There's a reason I'm in
this. wear that proudly. Um, yeah, don't
worry. He's dead now. He's dead now. Um,
the old racist is a dead man. Um, they
were ass dollars. Damn. And they smelled
so Oh, maybe he put the drugs in his ass
with the dollars. Uh, it's the in
between of ass and drugs. That makes
sense. That was totally racism, right?
Radio. That is 100% racism. 100%.
Goddamn. Right. Sorry, Slice. Hey,
you're on the late night stream, right?
It's got to be what? Past midnight where
you are. Sorry, we don't censor it this
time of night. Where is the chair? That
is a good question. I think somebody
might have walked away with the chair
for the night. We
>> Yeah, we we Yeah, the chair was in
character tonight. It wasn't the usual
chair. It was a different chair. Uh
putting money by your face. Hey, uh I
understand. But if if they get me with a
fented dollar, I'm ready to go, man. If
you got to worry about fentanyl being on
your dollar bills, dude, hey, take me
out. I'm good. Uh I barely wanted to be
here anyways. Maui. Damn, can't swim
that far. No, a lot of people can't. Uh,
as a matter of fact, very few people can
even kite kayak here. Some people died.
Um, how you know they didn't? That's a
good question. I'm still here though.
It's called Comedy Simulator because the
comedians simulate that they are doing
comedy. Yes, I go over in the beginning.
We're not real comedians. You're not a
real audience. Nobody's charging you
money. It's not a real comedy show.
Don't take it so seriously. That's the
That's the vibe of it. Uh, by putting
money by your face, wash your hands
after. Fen a lot of it. Um, yeah, fennel
hasn't really majorly hit Maui yet. Uh,
we do we are getting hot batches of Coke
here and there, but uh it's not out in
the wild as much. So, but thank you. I
will be more careful. Uh, Laura, I will
be more careful. Appreciate you,
especially in the mainland. Um, the
chair is in the corner like a baby. Yes.
Are you friends with The Rock every day?
No. Um, I would like to be. If you know
The Rock, reach out to him. Let them
know that we're out here doing comedy.
Uh, we all know that you appreciated the
comedy from the 1939 Germany. Um, no,
but I do appreciate cabaret from 1933.
See, if you know your cabaret, you'd get
that reference. Um,
the night off for the chair. Yeah, you
know, it takes a lot of [ __ ] Want to
make sure it had a moment. The chair. I
should call him. Dude, I love your guys
love for the chair. We need to give you
guys some like buttons or pendants or
something. What we got here?
>> Shane was almost as good as the chair
tonight. I will forward that silly ear.
Appreciate you. Um, also want to give a
shout out to uh Diablo. Just got some
sauce. I don't know if it reached you
yet. Should be arrive in there soon.
Thanks for watching and commenting fire.
Um, next week if you smell what Captain
Spaldin is cooking. That's right,
Diablo. Um, next week we'll do another
giveaway too. Um,
oh snap. Da wants to do a bump. Hey,
rail it up, bro. Hey, we're happy to be
here for you. I don't do drugs anymore,
but I wish I did. I'll be honest. I miss
them shits. Uh, that was really good.
Sick reference in the wild, dude.
Straight up, dude. We out here playing.
Fall asleep on the chair. Theme idea.
Kill Tony spoof. Were you active judge
of it? Uh, we advise judge each other.
Uh, we did do notes night, but that
would be a fun one. What would we call
that? Kill Chino. That feels like a
ripoff. Um, also my 40th birthday is
coming up in the beginning of October.
So, we'll be doing uh a roast chino, a
kill chino show uh probably that Monday
before I believe that is the seventh the
4th, October 4th. So, tune in and I'll
be reading the comments from on stage
about how mean you you guys want to be
to me, too. And uh hey guys, step it up
from like bald and old. All right. I
know I'm both. You can do better. I'm so
much easier to make fun of than that.
Um, what we got here?
Oh, Shane and Jackson should do a
impression of Bur and Ernie. I think I
have a Halloween dream. Thank you so
much for that, Allison. I appreciate
that. That's hilarious. This show made
you do drugs. I'm so sorry, Emperor. Uh,
but if you know what how relapse works,
nobody makes you relapse. Okay, you were
weak. We were just around. Uh, but also,
welcome back to the dark side. Uh, a
weekend of Bernies. Yeah, right. No
kidding. Uh, what we got? A theme could
be a roast that's not a showcase, you
know. Yeah, let everyone. Yeah, I agree.
I agree. Everybody roast me. Um, hey,
what's up, Kathy? Right on. Thanks for
watching from Las Vegas. Appreciate you.
Do I ever wipe and then smell my
fingers? Um, h
not my own. I mean, if somebody goes to
the bathroom, I ask them one or two, and
if they say two, I'm like, let me smell
your hands. Uh, just cuz I want to know.
Um, with bald and old. Yep. Candy Jack,
that's me, baby. I keep I keep it I keep
it slippery. Uh, fresh like a newborn.
Only you can get sober, too. Yeah. No,
I'm not. Yeah, that's true. Also on you
to get sober. Um,
>> I'm not like 100% sober. I don't I just
don't I smoke weed. Uh, I don't do
anything else really, though. Um, I I
drink a little bit, but I smoke weed.
That's about it. Um, every comic tonight
was infinitely funnier than Tony
Hinchcliffe. Hey, right on. Appreciate
it. Do I wipe from front to back or back
to front? That's a question directed at
me from Jimbo. He's asking me from the
back of the room. Right on. Have a good
night. See you tomorrow. Good to see you
guys.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Right on. Do I wipe from back to front,
front to back? Uh, I love that you
assume that I wipe. That's very nice. I
have a bedet. I drip dry like a lady.
That's how that works. Um,
>> I don't do more drugs. Now,
>> we got here.
>> Yeah, right, dude. Every time I talk
about drugs, my fingers like Here's the
thing. I used to have like a really good
drug table when I was living in LA.
Like, I set up my drug setup so that if
you had drugs in your pocket, they were
coming out. Like, my job, my goal was to
do all of your drugs. That's how much of
a drug problem I had. Uh, weed doesn't
count. No, but it does now because I
don't do anything else. Chino went to
Hawaii looking for a lei. Apparently,
nobody told him it was supposed to be
made out of flowers. A, that's sweet.
Um, did get a lelay, though. I am I am
in Hawaii. Yes, Antonio. I I am in
Hawaii. We're on the island of Maui at
Pa Bay Coffee and Bar on the Northshore.
Uh, I I I I'm 26. I just look older with
every bad joke. If that were true, I
would look even older than 40. I
guarantee it. Uh, you're at home naked,
Jimboa. Wow, that happened fast. You
couldn't wait to take your clothes off.
Um, back to front smelly tates forever.
Hey, B2B, appreciate you. Uh, keep that
taint stinky. I'll make sure Shane eats
it. Um, what do we got here? Dropped his
ice cream from Lilo and Stitch. I I
don't get that reference. Is there ice
cream for Lilo and Stitch? They always
give it to you guys before they give it
to us in Hawaii. That's the [ __ ] up
part. Um, here's my beef with Lilo and
Stitch. All right. The first Disney
Hawaii movie to come out that was like
really about our culture. What's Who's
the antagonist? Is it the aliens? No,
it's CPS.
How [ __ ] rude. You finally make a
movie about Hawaii culture and the first
people you incorporate are child
protective services. Very insensitive.
Uh, that kind of broke. It's also very
funny. Um, Stinky Taint is a lit
username idea. It really is, dude. Candy
Jack, appreciate you. Um, right on
everybody. I'm going to shut down the
stream for the night. I'm calling
tonight. Uh, it was a rough one as you
could tell. The live audience was rough.
Um, you guys were great. Uh, but rough
as always. 52K viewers tonight. Still a
good one for giving you absolute
nonsense nonsense. Um, appreciate
appreciate you guys. You got anything
left to say? Now say to me, two things
you'd like the never gold are. I'm glad
you appreciated the Charlie Kirk
reference. Uh, I'm GL. I could see it
split the chat in half. Some of you guys
liked it, some of you didn't. Um, but
you know, that's comedy these days. Uh,
there's no way to make everybody happy.
Everybody's picky. You're You're a lit
username idea. I love it. Right on,
guys. Have a great night. Love you. Bye.
Want to swing
from the chandelier here.
From the chandelier here.